{
    "subject": "resource/United_States_Military_Lands",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#comment",
    "object": "The United States Military Lands were land grants given to Continental Army servicemen by the United States Congress for service in the American Revolutionary War.The United States federal government was often short of money in the country's early decades.  The government's efforts to raise additional money in the early 1790s had met with considerable resistance, most notably the Whiskey Rebellion which had been provoked by a federal tax on whiskey.",
    "human_readable": "The comment about United States Military Lands states that they were land grants given to Continental Army servicemen by the United States Congress for service in the American Revolutionary War.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9119866490364075,
            "question": "Who received land grants as United States Military Lands?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8533179759979248,
            "question": "What was the purpose of granting United States Military Lands?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8251450657844543,
            "question": "Which organization granted the land for United States Military Lands?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8121119737625122,
            "question": "For what war were these land grants given?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8059463500976562,
            "question": "Were the land grants for United States Military Lands permanent?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7872987389564514,
            "question": "How did receiving United States Military Lands impact the lives of Continental Army servicemen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7703765034675598,
            "question": "What were United States Military Lands?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7163235545158386,
            "question": "When were these land grants given out?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5516722798347473,
            "question": "What does the statement tell us about the relationship between the government and its soldiers during the American Revolutionary War?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32607391476631165,
            "question": "Can you provide examples of how land granted under this program was used?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The comment about United States Military Lands states that they were land grants given to Continental Army servicemen by the United States Congress for service in the American Revolutionary War.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2087_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What does the statement tell us about the relationship between the government and its soldiers during the American Revolutionary War?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2087_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When were these land grants given out?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2087_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were United States Military Lands?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2087_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2087_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2087_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2087_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2087_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2087_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2087_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2087_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2087_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2087_91.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2087_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in JSON format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple, as it is explicitly stated that the United States Congress promised land grants to soldiers who served in the Continental Army during the American Revolutionary War."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents supports the statement that United States Military Lands, specifically referring to lands granted during the American Revolutionary War, were indeed land grants given to Continental Army servicemen by the United States Congress as a form of reward for their service. This is supported across multiple files which detail land grants and bounty land warrants issued to veterans of various conflicts including the Revolutionary War."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}